Gross, James A., Additional Research Files /4190
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
James A. Gross Additional Research Files
1969-1993
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Gross, James A.
/4190
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records (documents).
8036611
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 25, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 01, 2019
Biographical / Historical
Professor Gross teaches Labor Law, Labor Arbitration, and a course entitled Values, Rights and Justice in Economics, Law, and Industrial Relations. He received his B.S. from LaSalle College, M.A. from Temple University, and Ph.D. from University of Wisconsin.
Professor Gross is a member of National Academy of Arbitrators and on the labor arbitration panels of the American Arbitration Association, Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service and New York State Public Employment Relations Board, as well as being a panelist named in several contracts.[www.ilr.cornell.edu/directory/jag28/biography.htm]
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4057: James A. Gross NLRB Files /4057 P: James A. Gross NLRB Photographs /4124: James A. Gross Papers, Additional NLRB Research Files /4166: James A. Gross Additional NLRB Research Files /4186: James A. Gross Additional Research Files /4190: James A. Gross Additional Research Files 5697: James A. Gross Arbitration Files 5959: James A. Gross Additional Arbitration Files /4079: James A. Gross Additional Files
Gross, James A., 1933-; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations
8036611
- Ervin Committee, 1965-1988 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- NLRB Cases, Decisions, Criticisms of Decisions, etc., 1965-1974 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Edward Miller, 1970-1976 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Douglas Soutar Interview - Shelley Coppock, Interviewer, 1983-1990 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Nixon and implications for labor, 1970-1973 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Guide to Contents of Soutar Collection, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- National Labor Relations Board - Press Releases, 1955-1987 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- 50th Anniversary Conference (NLRB), 1984 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Duplicate of the Minutes of the 50th Anniversary Conference (NLRB), 1984 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Misc. Research Materials, 1961-1987 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Research Notecards (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Prof. Gross Research Notes, 1969-1993 (Box 2, Folder 3-4)